fast forward
Omitama delivery is now available.
It's the first live delivery in two weeks.
Ueda and Tomo...
Can you please stop being so absent on the air?
I mean, it's just something that's not right...
It's been a week since my last live mistress... two weeks...
Two weeks, that's a lot... at this time of the year.
There are rumors that if the show suddenly disappears, it's going to end like this...
I'm sad... or I've already fallen in a mountain... or some other bad rumors...
I'm in good health, I'm sorry, I'm in good health, I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
I'm sorry for making you wait so long... but this week I'm Master Aurora.
When have you not laughed?
I'm Master Aurora, your official business card.
Well, it just so happens that we came into the studio together today.
I thought I was alone and was about to close the elevator.
I thought I was alone and was about to close the elevator when he said, "FTES! I thought I was alone and was about to close the elevator.
I thought I was alone and was about to close the elevator when some ninja-looking guy came in.
I didn't know who he was.
He was wearing a hat!
I thought, "Who is this guy?
Domo
I hired you for a domo.
And I hired him once.
And one more time before.
I said good morning.
I guess I was too far gone.
I couldn't reach him.
So it was there before I got in?
Yes, sir.
Follow him like this.
I didn't notice it at all.
I was about to get in the elevator and push.
Oh! Like that.
I thought maybe he wouldn't notice me until we were face to face.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're a pro.
I'm a pro.
Thank you.
He's a ninja.
A ninja?
He's a kunoichi.
He's a kunoichi ninja.
It's kind of strange, isn't it?
Master Aurora, you really stand out, don't you?
No, you stand out a lot.
He stands out in so many ways.
How can he hide his presence only when he's like that?
Well, really.
It's only when it's me that my presence disappears.
When I go home, it doesn't disappear at all. It's only at the moment of entering.
I don't know why.
It's true that sometimes the members don't notice me when I'm outside.
Is that so?
They don't go to the front anymore.
You have to go to the front.
That's right.
It's the exact same case as earlier today, this morning.
He was dressed in a way I've never seen him before, so I thought, "Oh my God, he's a bad guy," and I was a little freaked out for a second, and then I pushed the button and said, "Oh, my God, he's a bad guy.
If it's that dangerous person, I'll go for the emergency services.
I was like "Master?
I'm basically in the same boat as you. I try to be as inconspicuous as possible.
I don't like to ride the elevator with other people.
So I can pretend I'm buying a juice from the vending machine.
I'll just put one down for you.
Then I'll go with you.
But as I get older, even doing that becomes a chore.
I've been in this state for a long time.
That's why they often talk about shyness in TV programs.
I'm shy," or "I'm shy around other people," they say.
Shyness is a strange thing.
If you're too shy, the situation reverses itself.
It's because I'm shy.
I can totally do it.
But I totally understand.
At least once.
Once you get over it, you can do it.
It's totally fine.
I don't feel anything.
I'm not nervous at all.
On the contrary.
I understand.
Maybe that's why... you don't understand.
You don't know what's going on.
It's because you don't know what's going on.
It's like, "Yay!
It's totally fine.
Amazing.
If I could read the air and know what's going on...
I'd be like, "Oh, shut up a little bit.
You can do it, can't you?
Yes, sir.
So...
Well, I think that's what it means.
That's great.
So you're saying they've reached it all at once?
This guy... he reached it too fast.
He's still so young.
If you were like me, you'd be fine.
The older I get...
You know, in cycles.
Like climate change.
It might come back again.
Maybe he'll come back.
I'm afraid of a very bright master.
I'll start with you.
The image is bright, though.
Oh, sure, sure.
That's true. That's why it's so strange.
That's what's so strange.
I don't mean that she's a bit brusque at all.
That's right.
It's more like...
Yes, it is.
How is it? But somehow she doesn't notice.
It's a miracle.
I'd like to go to the corner.
This has been a big hit. Where am I?
Here it comes! Here it is!
So, this time, what do you think?
I received a request from Ebitu-chan that she would like you to visit here.
By the way, first of all
I received this from Tamamin in Tama City, Tokyo.
I thought that Mr. Ebichu would probably understand.
By the way, it's OK if you can recognize this place by looking at the picture.
It's OK if you can recognize this place by looking at the photo, of course, but here is the proof of recognition.
I'll go there and take a picture from the same angle as the person who sent it to me.
It's like finding out where he was.
I'd like to find out where he was.
By the way...
In the last live broadcast, there was a glimpse of this.
I think I probably pretended to do so.
I think.
Why are you so quiet?
You're usually so loud.
Why don't you just answer what I say?
What's going on over there?
It's cold today.
What do they say about summer?
And then you say.
It's cold.
Then, they don't answer what we say.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
This is like the home of the shrimp chewers.
I think you can understand.
Just when I got this...
When I got this, Mayamaama was on shift.
I said, "I'm going out.
And he went.
You came?
May I?
The pictures that she took for me.
Thank you very much.
You've experienced so much.
It's a great experience.
Nice.
That's great!
Nice shot.
Nice.
This is
That's great.
That's exactly the same height.
Just like that.
Yes, yes, yes, we see this a lot.
But it's nice, isn't it?
Maybe it's the height difference.
It's like this.
A little bit.
It's a little bit lower.
It's the only height we've had before.
Tiny, tiny.
No, it's not.
It's like Arrietty.
It's too tiny.
Maybe like this.
If so, he's got quite a presence.
That's for sure.
Well, well, well...
There's one more problem with the shrimp, and that's the problem with the Sunflower 12, the Tokyo Meguro-kun.
It's a little far from Ebisu Station, but I've seen this place before.
I've been to the beach and I've been to the beach and I've been to the beach and I've been to the beach.
It's great, thank you!
I saw some unique buildings around Ebisu Station, right?
I see it... you're a great teacher.
I know that mountain very well.
I'm walking from this direction.
I have a good sense of geography.
Ebisu area is...
The Ebisu area...
It's great.
Ebisu area is cool.
Ebisu is so cool!
It's so cool!
So here are some pictures taken by Mai Mai Man!
Oh, wow!
The highest limit!
The person who sent this to me actually took this picture from the top of the train tracks.
There's a bridge with a wire fence.
A woman might not be able to get the camera out of the fence.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, it's only like this once before.
It's not that small.
It's very common.
It's the only one we've got.
It's only like this
Tiny.
Yeah, it's tiny.
I'm living temporarily.
We're living temporarily.
Yeah.
Heh.
The fence was a little taller than before, so I had to stand up really tall.
Ohhhh!
Ha-ha-ha!
Thank goodness!
I heard the photo of the fence is like this, too.
Indeed...
It means we have to go over the top of this net, right?
Indeed.
To take a beautiful picture
Like this
This and that....
Yes, that's right....
Real numbers are this close now.
Wow, wow, wow.
Tiny.
Long arms.
I went up there at 4:00.
Crab life.
Crunch!
Arrietty.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well.
Well, well, well... where are we?
And the Ebitujan.
How nice.
I mean, you know...
Shei-sho is surprisingly good at this.
I can't believe he's so good at it.
Maybe it's limited to the Ebisu area.
It's limited.
I see... I see...
That's amazing.
Let's go to that corner too, shall we?
A lot of places between stations.
Is this a hint?
Tricolor.
Zama City, Kanagawa Prefecture.
Thank you very much.
Creature Creation Corner
May I name the creature?
Yes, I do.
"Sleeping Beauty.
Naname Himeyoto.
What's a sunset sunbird?
I wonder.
Me, too, by the way.
Thank you.
What's the Himeyoto?
A slanted Himeyotou.
It's diagonal, isn't it?
Diagonal Princess Ruling Party.
What is the ruling party?
Yes, ma'am.
Hime Ruling Party.
Hime Ruling Party. What do you mean, "slant"?
About...
What's oblique about it?
By the way...
Various things...
Where am I?
They sent it to me.
They're coming from Machida, too.
I'm going there!
I want to go!
I do.
Please let me go.
I like the Machida area. It's interesting.
It's pretty cool.
I'm not from Machida.
I don't know where it is right away.
But there's a clue in the back.
There's a clue in the back.
It's tiny.
A building...
I don't know.
Where is it?
Yeah, Yokohama, overseas, too... they gave me one night there.
I lived as long as I could.
We'll be waiting for you.
But the joy I felt when I found this place... it's like...
That's right.
One thing I've been thinking...
People usually take pictures with their cell phones in portrait mode.
That's right.
I tend to take pictures horizontally because of my work.
Television is horizontal.
That's why I take pictures of people's faces.
I also take pictures of landscapes horizontally.
I'm shooting from the same place as the person who sent me the photos.
I thought something was different.
Maybe...
You shoot vertically.
Yes, that's right.
I learned a little bit about that, too.
It's true that when you look at it on a cell phone screen
It's easier to look at it vertically on a cell phone screen.
I'm learning a lot of things that I didn't know before.
I learned a lot of things I didn't know.
It's good.
Okay, so...
Please wait a moment.
diagonal
a secret sword
Secret Yotou
Yes, well, shall we go first master?
Yes, sir.
clap clap clap clap
Oh!
Is he a yurukyara?
Yurukyara.
Do you know what's going on?
Of course, it's diagonal.
The bird is at an angle.
Like this.
Is it safe for a bird to be in this condition?
They go through special training.
Then you have a bird like a TV man.
The muscles are connected to this area.
So it's always been this way.
It's the most comfortable.
On the other hand, if you do this or that, it's like you're tired.
The muscles don't have the same strength as before.
This is the only part of the body that's developed.
There's a screeching sound, like a bird.
I felt like there might be something there.
I felt like something was about to fly, like it was about to fly.
What is it?
What's this?
Me too...
Here's a hint...
I think it's seaweed.
I see...
Maybe it's seaweed.
Seaweed.
Maybe it's in the ocean.
That's what I mean.
Speaking of creatures in the sea that are in this state...
Turtles? Sea turtles?
I think it's a sea turtle.
Correct.
Yes!
You did it!
Correct.
What corner is this?
It was a turtle.
Turtles.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Hime-Yoshido.
Let's start with the princess/ruling party.
If we go to the Dragon's Palace, we can meet the Princess.
That's why...
I thought it might be a turtle.
I tried to make it appear from an angle.
Diagonally.
So if it doesn't appear from an angle, it's not a diagonal Princess Yotsuya.
It's a vertical Princess Yotsuya.
It depends on the angle.
If it's even on this side, it doesn't matter.
This time, she appeared from an angle, so it's a diagonal princess ruling party.
There are many other versions of Himeyotai, aren't there?
There are many versions of the Hime Yoto from the top.
There are various versions of HimeYotai from the top and HimeYotai from the right.
No, no, it's a pain in the ass.
I'll show you the standard for the human viewer.
Then the name changes completely, doesn't it?
Even within the same Himeyotai.
Even within the same Himeyoso.
It's amazing... it's like the king of success.
He keeps changing his name.
By the way, I've actually seen this one myself.
I have no idea what is "Nanamehimeyotou" when I saw the creature that gave me the correct answer.
There was no clue in the name.
I don't know, but I guess there must be something to it if a scholar went to all the trouble of naming it this way.
I've looked up a few descriptions that sound like it, but I can't find anything.
I'm wondering if any of you out there might be familiar with it.
It's a moth!
What a surprise!
This...
The name sounds like an insect.
Wow, you can draw it so realistically!
Yes, it was a little scary.
I just wanted to make you say, "Wow!
A little scary.
Put your heart into it.
It's a little scary.
Wow!
I don't know what to call it.
The whole thing is a bit light gray.
What do you mean by "diagonal"?
Well, the pattern is slanted, you could say that.
I'm talking about when you look at it from above, right?
So maybe it's like this... seven minutes after it appeared.
So it's just the princess ruling party.
It's just the princess's ruling party.
I'm sure it's just the princess ruling party.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I saw it again when I was writing this...
It's really amazing, isn't it?
It looks like eyeballs or something... or maybe it looks like it has seven eyes... or something.
I don't know how many eyes there are on the one covering the "7".
I think it's seven. I'm sorry, I don't know.
I'm sorry, I don't know, but it's not diagonal, it's diagonal. I see what you mean.
Himeyotai is probably the name of the head of the party. So I think there are lots of other Himeyotai.
This is somehow an oblique Himeyotou.
Was this a member of the Yoto group? Ah, I knew you could tell. She is a thief in the night.
That's right.
I know someone who knows a lot about it.
The kanji is slanted.
It's slanted here, too.
Then I knew there's a slant somewhere.
And then there are things like "fly diagonally" and so on.
It's always tilted a little bit.
Like when you're a long way from home.
I wonder if it's okay to play like that.
No, but you have that sense... but even if you make it cry like that...
Moths fly in strange ways, don't they?
They often fly like this... like this...
It flies like this.
I'm sorry, I can't predict it.
That's right.
I see.
Compared to butterflies, they're much bolder and their movements, including their patterns, are more animal-like.
It's more like a bird.
That's right.
More like an insect.
This one's really flapping her wings.
That's for sure.
Scary.
And it barely moves.
That's right.
It's stuck to the door.
That's true.
Well, well, well...
So that's how it is, isn't it?
Let's continue with the creation of creatures.
If you have any suggestions...
I'd like you to send them to me again.
I'd like to hear from you.
Yes, sir.
And with that...
Let's see...
What do you think?
To all the subscribers...
Long time no see.
It's been a while.
It's been weeks.
Good night.
It's been a while since I've been on a shift... and Master Aurora says it's been a while too.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Yes, I have a lot of work to do with Devil and other things related to Ebituaries, but when I'm not working what do you do?
what do you do when you're not working on your hobbies?
Oh...
I like to study as an adult.
I go to bookstores to look up things I'm interested in.
And look things up.
I search the Internet, but I also like to write things down in a notebook.
Now that I'm this age.
I skipped notebooks when I was in high school.
I wanted to write it down.
I've been doing a lot of research lately.
Compared to you two, I'm probably not from the internet generation
I'm not from the internet generation
I had a lot of opportunities to actually write things down.
Even now, I probably have more opportunities to write than most people.
I can't remember without writing.
I can't remember it without writing it down.
It's the same font as the rest of the web, isn't it, Mincho-University Gothic?
I just can't get into it.
I can read it, but...
But when you actually write it, it really comes through.
I think all people of the Showa generation are like that.
I think what he's doing is not wrong.
I don't think it's wrong.
I think the human brain has a sense that it's a form that can be taken in.
It's like we can take it in as a form.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's what's left.
I'm sure you can check the set and get in right away.
And then it goes in with the urine.
And then it's gone.
It's going to fall out.
I can't help but feel that it's just going to fall out.
But that's probably because of the difference in lifestyle.
I'm not used to this way.
If you're used to writing this way, you can write the other way around.
Because there's a cushion.
You might not be able to remember.
I'm not trying to say that one is right or the other.
It's just that you should choose the one that's more interesting for you.
This is true.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm studying.
I like to think about it.
You didn't study much when you were in school?
I really hated it.
I was really kind of elite in elementary school.
I don't call myself elite.
Elite people don't call themselves elite.
I got a lot of 100s and stuff. I was good at math.
I was good at math, arithmetic, arithmetic.
History.
I wasn't that good, but I liked science.
And my brother was smart, too.
I had a feeling I could go to college or something.
But more than that, I found something I was crazy about.
I told him I didn't need anything else.
He boldly threw it all away.
Then, what is it?
Maybe he's smart to begin with.
I don't feel that at the moment.
For now.
But you are.
I'm often told I'm not very smart.
That's terrible!
That's terrible.
You shouldn't say that.
That's right.
I get that a lot.
But you're very aware of it.
I don't know how to say it.
I don't know if it's the family I was born into or what, but I don't think I'm in the middle of the world.
But I'm the type of person who doesn't understand that this is normal, that everyone is like this, and when we're all talking on mc, for example, I'm the type of person who can't notice anything unusual.
For example, when we were all talking on mc, I'm the type of person who can't notice anything unusual, or the type of person who thinks that everyone else, including the fans and the members, think something is unusual, but I don't think it's unusual, so I just go on with it.
I think it's a little bit different.
I'm sure there's a lot of that going on... but it's like he's in charge of everything... and when something unusual happens... he just says, "If I panic here, everyone will be upset... so I need to calm down.
It's not funny if you don't participate in the happenings.
I mean, it's like, "Oh, no, I'm not in the mood for this.
I'm not sure why it's so hard to understand, but it's fun to see so many different kinds of people.
I'm sure you're right...
sunset on Zaradar... to the first Devil in a long time... and to Master Aurora... who's making a lot of money.
Yui-san, thank you for working hard for the first time in a long time!
new hair Thank you for saying it's cute!
Master Takumi, you're so cute!
I'm not sure if it's the cute mouth or the lipstick on the mirror that says "I like you".
I'm not writing "master is good" in lipstick on the mirror, but the last letter is "bee" and there's another word that sounds like it's about to fall over.
I'm going to study hard.
I'm sure you can do it. Em Nagaoka-san, go for it, master.
I got a message of support.
It made me want to cheer for you.
I love it... you're getting all kinds of certifications.
What if you take this momentum and apply to college? I'd like to go to college... but college?
They say you can go to college at any age.
I guess there is something to be said for going at that age, isn't there?
Well, I guess it depends on the field.
Humanities and sciences are totally different, and even in the sciences, there are some that are related to this nowadays.
So there are a lot of specialists in a wide range of fields.
I mean, there are a lot of people who are specialists in that field...
I've heard that even after they get old, they can still come in.
I think it's totally possible.
You can go there.
I want to go to school.
When you pass the entrance exam, let's get close to you.
Maybe when they announce the acceptance...
How do you like it? I'll tell you what.
Please, please, please.
There it is! I failed!
You fell out!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Well, well, well, well, well, well...
By the way, I'll be back next week for another live broadcast.
I'll be back! I'll be back.
I'm back.
I'm back and I'm back.
I'm sure they'll be flying around again.
They're wondering if Master is finally dead.
All kinds of rumors.
Rough rumors.
Maybe Master embezzled money from the company.
Rough rumors...
But...
That's not what I meant.
I'd like to read the article about you and Yango.
The article with Mr. Yango.
I'm just going to muddle through here.
I heard there's going to be some kind of special program.
A special program?
No, it's not.
Well, well, well.
Embezzlement?
What?
Yeah, yeah.
Think about another show.
Another show?
It's a combination of things.
A lot of things.
A combination.
Combination?
Why are we doing that one?
No, no, no.
I just thought it'd be cool.
It's cool.
I see.
I like how it reads.
Even though they're sideways.
It's like it's read phonetically.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well.
Mr. Meat Tomato...
Master, it's been a long time since I've had a part-time job.
You look so cute today, I love it.
I love you.
They're all sending messages of love.
What's going on?
Is it Derekie, everyone?
I mean, we're all getting paid through these things now, right?
I mean, they're getting paid now, right?
That's right.
That means I was irresistible.
I'm irresistible now.
You're already irresistible here.
That's right.
Then maybe my irresistible key is now.
No, no, no.
Here.
That's why.
No, no, no.
But, well...
It's definitely a "motel key.
It's definitely a "mote key.
Thank God.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right, well, I'll see you next week for a week.
I'll let you talk to him.
And then the next week...
It'll be business as usual.
Well, thank you all very much for your time this week.
Thank you very much.
It says, "Irresistible.